{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": {
        "theme": [
          {
            "Question": "How many players can you have in a multiplayer game of The Sims 4?",
            "TrueAnswer": "4",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "2",
              "6",
              "8"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The Sims 4 allows up to 4 players to play online in the multiplayer mode."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which studio developed the game 'Cities: Skylines'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Colossal Order",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Maxis",
              "Paradox Interactive",
              "Blizzard Entertainment"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Colossal Order, a Finnish game development studio, is behind the city-building game 'Cities: Skylines'."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the primary resource in 'RimWorld'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Food",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Gold",
              "Wood",
              "Iron"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'RimWorld' requires players to manage food to sustain their colony amidst various challenges and events."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which of these is a popular farming game franchise?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Harvest Moon",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Final Fantasy",
              "Assassin's Creed",
              "Grand Theft Auto"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Harvest Moon is a long-running farming simulation game series that has gained a dedicated fanbase."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which game allows players to manage their own theme park?",
            "TrueAnswer": "RollerCoaster Tycoon",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim",
              "Overwatch",
              "Minecraft"
            ],
            "Explanation": "RollerCoaster Tycoon lets players construct and manage their own amusement park, creating rides and managing finances."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'The Sims', what is the highest career level in the Culinary track?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Celebrity Chef",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Sous Chef",
              "Executive Chef",
              "Pastry Chef"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The Celebrity Chef career level is the highest rank in 'The Sims' Culinary career track, granting special perks and benefits."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which virtual life game is known for its quirky humor and characters?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Stardew Valley",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt",
              "Fallout 4",
              "The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Stardew Valley's charming characters and humorous moments contribute to its endearing and captivating gameplay experience."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which genre does 'Euro Truck Simulator 2' belong to?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Simulation",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Role-Playing",
              "First-Person Shooter",
              "Puzzle"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Euro Truck Simulator 2' falls under the simulation genre, offering players a realistic truck driving experience across Europe."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'Planet Coaster', what are players tasked with building?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Amusement Parks",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Space Stations",
              "Underwater Cities",
              "Medieval Castles"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Players in 'Planet Coaster' create and manage elaborate amusement parks with custom-designed rides and attractions."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which game simulation involves creating and managing a hospital?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Two Point Hospital",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "FIFA 22",
              "Call of Duty: Warzone",
              "Horizon Zero Dawn"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Two Point Hospital' challenges players to construct and oversee an efficient healthcare facility with quirky illnesses."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What farming mechanic is a core feature of 'Story of Seasons'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Seasonal Crops",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Livestock Breeding",
              "Fishing",
              "Mining"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The farming cycle in 'Story of Seasons' revolves around planting and harvesting crops based on seasonal variations and weather."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'Airport CEO', what type of facility do players manage?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Airports",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Shopping Malls",
              "Sports Arenas",
              "Zoos"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Airport CEO' simulates the intricate management of airport operations, including logistics, security, and passenger services."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the goal in 'Prison Architect'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Build and Manage a Prison",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Design a Theme Park",
              "Lead an Army to Victory",
              "Run a Cafe"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Players in 'Prison Architect' assume the role of a prison designer and manager, overseeing inmate needs and maintaining security."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which simulation game tasks players with overseeing a space agency's expansion?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Kerbal Space Program",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Assassin's Creed Valhalla",
              "The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt",
              "Minecraft"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'Kerbal Space Program' lets players control a space program, designing and launching spacecraft for missions."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the primary objective in 'The Escapists'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Escape from Prison",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Start a Small Business",
              "Conquer Enemy Territories",
              "Solve Mysteries"
            ],
            "Explanation": "In 'The Escapists', players strive to plan and execute clever strategies to escape from incarceration."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In the game 'House Flipper', what do players renovate?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Houses",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Hotels",
              "Castles",
              "Amusement Parks"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'House Flipper' tasks players with purchasing and renovating various houses to sell for profit."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which genre does 'Microsoft Flight Simulator' belong to?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Flight Simulation",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Racing",
              "Point-and-Click Adventure",
              "Platformer"
            ],
            "Explanation": "As a classic flight simulation game, 'Microsoft Flight Simulator' offers a realistic aviation experience with accurate recreations of real-world locations."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the main focus of 'The Isle' game?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Survival",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "City Building",
              "Racing",
              "Fashion Design"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'The Isle' immerses players in a survival experience, challenging them to thrive in a prehistoric environment as dinosaurs or humans."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which of these is a staple feature in 'SimCity' games?",
            "TrueAnswer": "City Planning and Management",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Space Exploration",
              "Detective Investigations",
              "Pirate Adventures"
            ],
            "Explanation": "SimCity games emphasize urban planning and governance, allowing players to build and manage virtual cities."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the central theme of the game 'House Party'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Social Interactions",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Monster Hunting",
              "Space Exploration",
              "Time Travel"
            ],
            "Explanation": "'House Party' focuses on navigating social interactions and relationships at a raucous house gathering with various characters."
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}